[{"answer": "One of the reasons I wanted to speak to him, I wanted to speak to him as a father, one father to another father.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "When you walked into the room and there is the father of this young man who took your daughter's life, what goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "I don't think there is any one particular theme that spit out more than another.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Did you get any kind of insight into what may have been the main trigger here?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Not particularly, no.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Had he been able to work out in his head what had happened to his son?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "It's definitely a kind of a step in this process.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Do you have it in your heart to forgive Adam Lanza for what he did or is that simply a step too far?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Speaking from my own experience, which is all I can do, is just say that whenever something happens in your life that you're faced to make that kind of hard decision, and it changes your outlook on the entire world, then it needs to make some kind of a change within you.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Without getting into any detail of any of the gun control debate, do you think that particularly the politicians who it seems to many people are making decisions based around protecting their political lives, if you like, over their principle, do you think if any of them had had to go through what you and your family have gone through, what any of the families of Sandy Hook, you think they would make decisions like that in a different way?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "I definitely feel lucky to have her.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Do you feel lucky to have each other?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "The best thing we have been able to come up with is when you go through something like this and there will be that many emotions, you mentioned a whole list of emotions, all of those can happen to you in a single day or one of those emotions can take over your life for weeks at a time.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "I mean, do you have a mechanism to cope?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "The morning after Emilie died, I was greeted by my other two daughters, I knew that I had a reason to continue in this life and I knew that they were my reason to get up that morning and to continue to be the best dad that I can be.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Is that a sign that you might be able to have some kind of life going forward, that perhaps didn't seem possible a couple months ago?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "I think it's very important to be open about it.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "What can you say as a father and indeed, Alissa as a mother, to the two little ones about what happened to their big sister?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "ARKER: She embodied so much in her life.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "What do you want her legacy to be?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, in this country, laws have to abide by the constitution of the state that they're enacted in as well as under the federal Constitution.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Well, I would hope the British folks talk about it as much.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Or do you?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "If we didn't have the guns, who would you have turned to?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Just say thank you.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Where was Winston Churchill when all this was going on?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "I've heard about 20,000.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "How many existing gun control laws are there in America, do you know?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Now, Piers --", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Do you know how many?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Here's the point.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Do you know how many?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "-- back in January, if you focus on the gun, you miss the opportunity to zero in on the problem, which is never the gun per se, but always in whose hands are the guns.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Do you know an answer or not?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "I want to talk about your body, as I always do when you come in to be interviewed by me, because you look ripped in this movie.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Hey, how are you?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "But did you like that story line, of the redemption, this incredibly capable, slightly tormented agent?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Well, they're amazing individuals.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "What was that like?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "That is me trying to get a job.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "The obvious question is, what on Earth are you two up to?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "It was for charity.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "This was actually for charity, right?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Banning is ex-special forces, Ranger battalion.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: How do we know we can trust this?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Great.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "How are you now all?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Great movie.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I think absolutely.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Did you think it would be good to have more women in the top roles of government?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "It makes it looks like it's manly, it's powerful to have a gun and you may get away with whatever you want to get away with?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "He wants to now and I try to hold it at bay.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "How do you feel as a parent?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "You've got to admit, we do.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Where is it?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Yeah, he is, and a very nice guy.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "He's a bit of a heartthrob, isn't it?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "A hundred percent.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I can't think of anybody better.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Are you thinking what I'm thinking?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Would any actor turn that down?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "A billion dollar franchise?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "You've still got a refuge of it.", "docId": "130322pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "What Scottish accent?", "qSentId": 546}]